

Amin Alian

Aminager | In Amin Alian | Alian | Alianamin | Alianamin | In the Aminager | In Amin Alian | Alianamin | In the Alianamin | In

SUMMARY

Hey! My name is Amin and I'm currently in my seventh semester at LTH, studying Computer Science Engineering, specialising in Software. I'm fluent in Swedish, English and Persian. Being around people gives me energy, but my foremost quality is my calm. I relax by playing sports and am looking forward to new and ambitious tasks.

Work Experience

Tetra Pak, Student Talent Programme

Jun 2022 - present

I am a technical expert at Tetra Pak on the Microsoft Ecosystem, such as PowerApps, Power BI and Power Automate. I have created my own reports in Power BI which are used in the engineers daily work. In PowerApps I also developed apps by configuring a back-end and creating a front-end to reduce the time loss in their daily work.

DHL Express, Courier

Jun 2021 - Aug 2021

As a courier the daily tasks were very independent and individual. This meant that I had to use critical thinking and challenge myself to solve difficulties and problems that arose everyday. My biggest takeaway from the position was how much of a difference it makes to allow myself to ask questions. By collaborating and sharing knowledge we achieved more.

EDUCATION

2019 - present (2024) MSE Comp. Sci. at Lund University, LTH

(GPA: 3.3/4.0)

2016 - 2019

Upper Secondary School at Kungsholmens Gymnasium

(GPA: 20.8/22.5)

Voluntary Work

Vice Chairman of the Activity Committee, Comp Sci Guild LTH

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

As the Vice Chairman I arranged and executed events together with other guilds at LTH. I was ultimately in charge of organisation of events and integration in the guild.

Web master, Student Union at Kungsholmens Gymnasium

Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

I was in charge of making sure the website was maintained, developed and secure

SKILLS

Programming

I am very comfortable with programming and approaching new tasks. I have university experience in working with Scrum, Agile and team development. I am most comfortable in Python and Java, but I am eager to learn more. I have worked in Scala, React as well as PowerQuery and DAX as well.

Last updated: October 11, 2022